Guide to the Jack Doroshow / Flawless Sabrina Papers MSS.594
Fales Library and Special Collections
- Series II. Drag Events and Ephemera, 1960-2014; 8.5 Linear Feet in 6 manuscript boxes, 3 flat boxes, 2 flat-file folders, 2 custom flat boxes, and 1 shared box; 13 Gigabytes in 52 computer files
  This series includes paper and electronic files related to the career of drag queen Flawless Sabrina, as well as files collected by Sabrina on the drag community in general dating from the 1960s to the 2010s. Flawless Sabrina material includes appearance photographs, invitations, and announcements. The series also contains show planning material including production notes, stage directions, and large scrolls containing dialogue cues for skits.
  Digital and print photographs in this series include Flawless Sabrina with friends, drag queens, at events, and professional portraits of Sabrina by Diane Arbus, Julia Nuson, Ves Pitts, and Sabrina's partner, Curtis Carman. Large photograph collages previously mounted on Sabrina's apartment walls are in this series, featuring images of Sabrina, friends, events, other performers, dating from the 1980s to the 2010s. This series also has a number of artists' drawings and paintings of Flawless Sabrina, while other artists were inspired to include her in a number of video and photographic installations. This series contains video recordings, catalogs, and photographs of some of these art installations including Dorian, a Cinematic Perfume; Jack and Debra which includes footage of Flawless Sabrina juxtaposed with scenes from a Miss America Pageant; and Irma Vep, The Last Breath by Michelle Handelman. An event announcement and video recording of the 2014 NYU Tisch School lecture event featuring Flawless Sabrina sharing her experiences as a drag queen is in this series as well as video footage of her 74th birthday party in 2013 at the Soho Grand. Objects in the series include sequin pants with "Flawless" stamped on the side, and a rubber stamp with "Mother Approved, XO" in reference to Sabrina's other name, Mother Flawless Sabrina.
  This series also contains material accumulated by Flawless Sabrina on drag performers and the community including books; press clippings; publications; city event guides; event invitations; wig catalogs; headshots and bios of performers. Of note is a 1960s photograph album containing performers in drag shows, but also men dressed in casual women's clothes at leisure in various private homes. This series also includes video footage from the 1970s of vacationers on Fire Island and in Central Park in New York, and a 2011 Joe Jeffreys recording of the 46th Annual Miss Fire Island Contest.
  - Photographs -- Shows, Pageants, Home Parties, and Informal Gatherings with Flawless Sabrina, Performers, and Others, 1960-1964 (Box 9, Folder 14)
  - Photographs by Frank Teti -- Portraits of Flawless Sabrina, circa 1967-1968 (Box 9, Folder 15)
  - Photographs by Diane Arbus -- Portraits of Flawless Sabrina, 1968; cuid39112 (Box 9, Folder 16, Box Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_594_ER_2)
  - Photographs -- Portraits and Early Images of Flawless Sabrina, 1968, undated (Box 9, Folder 17)
  - Press Clippings and Articles re: Drag Queens and Performers, 1969, 1995, 2008 (Box 9, Folder 18)
  - Book -- How to Impersonate a Woman, 1973 (Box 9, Folder 19)
  - Footage by Nelson of Scenes from Fire Island (1976) and Central Park in New York (1973), TV Advertisements, and Footage of David Bowie, 1973, 1976, undated; cuid39120 (Box Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_594_ER_8)
  - Photographs -- Performers and Friends at Shows, Parties, Parades, 1973-2009 (Box 10, Folder 1, Box 50, Folder 6)
  - Wigs and Hair -- Catalogs and Press Clippings, 1980s, 1999 (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - The Rocky Horror Poster Magazines, 1980 (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - Dietz Productions -- Proposals and Agreements for Entertainment Booking, Announcements for Flawless Sabrina Private Party, 1982 (Box 10, Folder 4-5)
  - Flawless Sabrina Event Announcements and Promotional Material, 1980s (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - Flawless Sabrina Event -- "A Reading of Beads" Announcements, Photographs, and Promotional Material, 1999, undated (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - Flawless Sabrina Event Announcements and Promotional Material, 2000-2017, undated (Box 10, Folder 8-10)
  - Drag and Related Event Announcements and Promotional Material, 1980s-2010s, undated (Box 10, Folder 11-12, Box 11, Folder 1-7, Flat-file-folder 5)
  - Book -- What a Drag, 1984 (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - Angela Repellant (Angela Pringle) -- Performer Press Packet and Writings, 1986 (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - Caskillet Review at the Shark Club -- Event Script, Shark Sketches, circa 1986 (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - Various City Weekly Gay Event Guides, 1986-1987 (Box 11, Folder 11)
  - Sketches and Drawings of Flawless Sabrina, 1987, undated (Box 12, Folder 1, Box 50, Folder 7, Box 51, Folder 10)
  - Private Lives Event Guide Signed by Cover Model Wayland Flowers, December 1988 (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - Book -- Drag Gags, 1991 (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - My Comrade -- Flawless Sabrina Featured, 1993, 2004, 2006 (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - Photograph -- Portrait of Flawless Sabrina, 1995 (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - Poop Joke Newsletter, February-March 1998 (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - Propaganda Magazine, Winter 1999 (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - Photographs -- Flawless Sabrina with Others at Events, Shows, and Parties, 1999-2009, undated (Box 12, Folder 8, Box 50, Folder 4)
  - Drag Performer Bios and Headshot Photographs, 2000, undated (Box 12, Folder 9-10)
  - Photographs by Curtis Carman -- Flawless Sabrina with Friends Lavynia, Mike, Brandon, and Barbara, 2000 (Box 12, Folder 11)
  - Photograph Collages with Flawless Sabrina and Others, 2000, undated (Box 12, Folder 12, Flat-file-folder 4, Flat-file-folder 5)
  - Cards, Announcements, Press Clippings from Disassembled Collage, undated (Box 12, Folder 13)
  - Photographs by Curtis Carman -- Portraits of Flawless Sabrina, 2000-2001 (Box 12, Folder 14)
  - Flawless Sabrina Website Printed Pages, Press Clippings, 2001, 2017 (Box 12, Folder 15)
  - Book -- The Art of Conversation, 2002 (Box 12, Folder 16)
  - Photographs -- Flawless Sabrina Performing, Posing, Socializing, 2002-2005, undated (Box 12, Folder 17, Box 50, Folder 1)
  - Photograph Collage of Flawless Sabrina from Leslie Lohman Art Installation, 2004 (Box 12, Folder 18)
  - Photographs -- Flawless Sabrina Appearance at the Tritone in Philadelphia, PA, 2004-04-25 (Box 12, Folder 19)
  - Next Magazine, 2006-04-14 (Box 12, Folder 20)
  - "Kings and Queens of New York City: A Drag Summit" -- Program, Promotional Material, and Correspondence, 2006 (Box 12, Folder 21)
  - Photographs -- Flawless Sabrina and Others at Event, 2006; cuid39116 (Box Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_594_ER_3)
  - Makeup Artist Michael Gwaltney -- Portfolio of Work, 2006; cuid39117 (Box Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_594_ER_4)
  - Advertisement for Visual AIDS with Flawless Sabrina Image by Curtis Carman, 2006 (Box 12, Folder 22)
  - Flawless Sabrina Brief Bio, circa 2006-2017 (Box 12, Folder 23)
  - Gazelland Magazine, Spring 2007 (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - Dame Edna -- Show Programs, Promotional Material, 2007, undated (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - Drag Show Video Vrit -- Promotional Material, Program, Press Clippings, 2007-2011 (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - Flawless Sabrina Images in Publications, 2007-2012 (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - Video Art Installation Dorian, a Cinematic Perfume Featuring Flawless Sabrina -- Program, Photographs, and Press Clippings, 2009, 2012 (Box 13, Folder 5, Flat-file-folder 5)
  - Artworks by Flawless Sabrina -- Images and Artist Statement, 2010 (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - Joe Jeffreys Footage of Rita and Charity at the 46th Annual Miss Fire Island Contest, 2011-09-10; cuid39121 (Box Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_594_ER_9)
  - Video Art Installation -- Jack and Debra, 2012-09-25; cuid39119 (Box Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_594_ER_7)
  - Flawless Sabrina 74th Birthday Celebration at Soho Grand, 2013-09-10; cuid39118 (Box Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_594_ER_6)
  - The Missing Queen Ball -- List of Performers, 2013 (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - Artwork Irma Vep, The Last Breath by Michelle Handelman, Featuring Images for Flawless Sabrina -- Exhibit Catalogues, 2014 (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - "In Conversation with Flawless Sabrina" Event at NYU Tisch School -- Announcement and Video Recording, 2014-11-14; cuid39113 (Box 13, Folder 9, Box Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_594_ER_5)
  - Stage Direction Notes for Show, undated (Box 13, Folder 10)
  - Notes -- "Bits for Backer's Audition", undated (Box 13, Folder 11)
  - Flawless Sabrina Written Advice to Performer, undated (Box 13, Folder 12)
  - Cue Cards / Script for Shows, undated (Box 13, Folder 13, Box 51, Folder 8)
  - Flawless Mother Sabrina's Fairytale Theater Presents: All About Steve -- Script Section, undated (Box 13, Folder 14)
  - Portion of Script re: Nurse and Doctor, undated (Box 13, Folder 15)
  - Artwork -- Cardboard Cutout of Flawless Sabrina Head, undated (Box 13, Folder 16)
  - Publication -- Dr. Ducky DooLittles, undated (Box 13, Folder 17)
  - Photographs -- Unknown Drag Event, undated (Box 13, Folder 18)
  - Photographs -- Flawless Sabrina and Performers at Drag Events, undated (Box 13, Folder 19)
  - Photographs -- Interiors of Event Venue, Exterior of Silver Platter Club, undated (Box 13, Folder 20, Box 50, Folder 1)
  - Photograph by Julia Nuson -- Portrait of Flawless Sabrina, undated (Box 13, Folder 21)
  - Photographs by Ves Pitts -- Jack Doroshow Transforming into Flawless Sabrina, undated (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - Club 82 Souvenir Photograph of Drag Performers, undated (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - Live Shows -- Script Scrolls, undated (Box 52, Box 53)
    Physical Characteristics and Technical Requirements
    Due to the fragile nature of the materials, Public Services staff must remove these items from boxes and provide guidance on handling.
  - Unknown Show "Saturday Night Line Up" List, undated (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - Flawless Sabrina-Inspired Print Advertisements and Art, undated (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - Flawless Sabrina Art Plaque; "Sis" Crushed Soda Can Necklace; "Mother Approved" Ink Stamp, undated (Box 48)
  - "Flawless" Logo Black Sequin Pants, undated (Box 49)
  - Birthday Note and Get Well Card with Flawless Sabrina Sketch, undated (Box 50, Folder 1)
  - Large Photograph Collages -- Flawless Sabrina and Friends, undated (Box 51, Folder 6-7)
  - Show Poster -- "Gimme a Drag!!", undated (Box 51, Folder 9)
  - Performance -- The Emperor's Premiere, undated; cuid39122 (Box Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_594_ER_11)
  - Music Disc with Artwork -- "House of Music Flawless Mix Disc" With Track List, undated (Box 44, Folder 12)
- Series III. Writings, 1968-2017; 13 Linear Feet in 21 manuscript boxes, 1 flat box, 1 oversize flat box, 1 flat-file folder, and 1 shared box
  This series contains Doroshow's writings including scripts, articles, reviews, notes, and proposed books. Of note in this series is a significant and rare collection of over 80 issues of the publication Michael's Thing, a weekly guide to New York City and a benficial resource of listings for clubs and businesses connected to the gay community during the 1970s and 1980s. Doroshow was a contributing writer for this publication. Michael's Thing offered celebrity interviews, articles, film reviews, party announcements, and advertisements for clubs and amenities for the gay community, dating from the 1970s to the 2000s. This subseries also contains a large number of Doroshow's legal pads, notebooks, sketch pads, and loose notes kept throughout his lifetime, filled with fragments of writing ideas, sketches, production notes, brief journal entries, quotes (his and others), and grocery and to do lists. This series also contains proposals for Doroshow's books, How to Enjoy Gay Sex and Flawless Sabrina's Cooking Guide for Single Men, neither of which were published.
  - Flawless Sabrina's Cooking Guide for Single Men -- Book Proposal, 1968-1972 (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - Betty Moon -- Play Script, 1969-08-13 (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - Michael's Thing -- Publication, 1972-1987 (Box 14, Folder 7-12, Box 15, Folder 1-8, Box 16, Box 17, Folder 1-9)
  - How to Enjoy Gay Sex -- Book Proposal, 1972 (Box 18, Folder 1)
  - Notebooks, Notes, 1972-2008 (Box 18, Folder 2-9, Box 19, Folder 1-7, Box 20, Folder 1-9, Box 21, Folder 1-8, Box 22, Folder 1-6)
  - Notebooks, Notes, 2006, 2014, undated (Box 51, Folder 11-12)
  - Notebooks, Notes, 2008-2017 (Box 23, Folder 1-6, Box 24, Folder 1-10, Box 25, Folder 1-7, Box 26, Folder 1-5, Box 27, Box 28)
  - Notebook -- Sketch, Quotes, Ideas, 2016-2017 (Box 47)
  - Notebooks, Notes -- Budgets, undated (Box 28, Folder 7)
  - Notebooks, Notes -- Cooper Union Show, undated (Box 28, Folder 8)
  - Notebooks, Notes -- Production Notes, undated (Box 28, Folder 9)
  - Notebooks, Notes -- "Show Biz Stories", undated (Box 29, Folder 1)
  - Notebooks, Notes / Show Cue Card -- "Telephone Jeopardy" Skit, undated (Box 29, Folder 2, Flat-file-folder 5)
  - Notebooks, Notes -- Journal Entries, undated (Box 29, Folder 3)
  - Notebooks, Notes -- Sketches and Notes, undated (Box 29, Folder 4)
  - Notebooks, Notes -- Writing Ideas, undated (Box 29, Folder 5-7, Box 30, Folder 1-6, Box 31, Folder 1-4)
  - Notebooks, Notes, undated (Box 31, Folder 5, Box 32, Folder 1-7, Box 33, Folder 1-4)
  - Autobiographical Entries / Writings, circa 1980s (Box 33, Folder 5)
  - The Hostage -- One Act Play Script, 1985 (Box 33, Folder 6)
  - Writings / Lyrics re: Roy Orbison, 2009 (Box 33, Folder 7)
  - Why Bother Part Ten, 2009 (Box 33, Folder 8)
  - "Wise Cracks" in Papercut Annual 2013 (Box 33, Folder 9)
  - Review / Notes re: Zachary Drucker's Short Film, 2016 (Box 33, Folder 10)
  - Chapters from Untitled Book / Script, undated (Box 34, Folder 1-4)
  - "Kaum Documentary Tape Transcript, Corrected", undated (Box 34, Folder 5)
  - Unknown Dialogue, Parts of Writings, Writing Samples, undated (Box 34, Folder 6)
  - Writings -- Poem, Cue Cards, undated (Box Shared Fales 086, Folder 19)
- Series IV. Business Projects, 1965-2012; 1.5 Linear Feet in 3 manuscript boxes
  This series contains material related to Doroshow's many business ventures over the years to support himself while also pursuing his entertainment projects and drag performances. This series includes files from his antique consignment business from the 1960s to the early 2000s. These files typically contain lists of items and prices, receipts, slide images of artworks, and correspondence. Other less successful businesses include plans and correspondence for a club in the Chrysler Building in 1987, and correspondence and advertisements for the sale of children's puppet quilts in 1983. Doroshow also attempted to start two magazines, Reflections and Casina. Files on these two publishing ventures include proposal packets, correspondence, and mock-up issues.
  - Antique and Artwork Consignment Business, 1965-2003 (Box 34, Folder 7-8, Box 35, Folder 1-4)
  - Talent Manager -- Rachel Harlow Contract, Press Clippings, 1968-1988 (Box 35, Folder 5)
  - Talent Manager -- Elaine Fulkerson Contract, 1968 (Box 35, Folder 6)
  - Publication -- Reflections -- Proposal, circa 1975 (Box 35, Folder 7)
  - Adam's Apple Restaurant -- Waiter Guidelines, Procedures, 1975 (Box 35, Folder 8)
  - Publication -- Casino -- Proposal, Mock-up Issue, Correspondence, 1976 (Box 35, Folder 9)
  - Business Opportunities -- Brochures, Releases, 1976-1985 (Box 36, Folder 1)
  - Marketing Consulting -- WJNL TV Station, 1978-1979 (Box 36, Folder 2)
  - Baird Jones Club -- Passes, Research Material, 1980s (Box 36, Folder 3)
  - Reference for Jack Doroshow for Unknown Project, 1982 (Box 36, Folder 4)
  - Magic Puppet Quilts -- Advertisements, Marketing Letters, 1983 (Box 36, Folder 5)
  - Art Sales -- Johnathan Rogers Clark Exhibition Catalogs, Scrapbook, 1984-2002 (Box 36, Folder 6)
  - Plans for a Club in the Chrysler Building -- Proposal, Plans, 1987 (Box 36, Folder 7)
  - Publication -- Cooking in Heels by Koi Doroshow, 2012 (Box 36, Folder 8)
  - Notes on Concepts and Ideas for Clubs, undated (Box 36, Folder 9)
- Series V. Music Production, 1970-1987; 1 Linear Feet in 2 manuscript boxes
  This series contains material on Doroshow's work as a music producer, mostly taking place in France and England during the 1970s and 1980s. Work files contain notes, album storyboards, promotional material, and agreements between artists and recording companies, including X-15 Productions, Rise Entertainment, and London Records. Artists represented by Doroshow include Claudia Ashley, Claudia Polley, and Sasha Rage.
  - Blank Music Producing Contracts, 1970s (Box 36, Folder 10)
  - Music Artist Bio -- Vincent Buffa, 1970s-1980s (Box 36, Folder 11)
  - Chris De Marco Album Gigolo -- Contract, 1976 (Box 36, Folder 12)
  - Robyn "Charly" Peterson for Album Danc'in in the Nude -- Contract, Press Release, Images, 1976 (Box 36, Folder 13)
  - Flipers Album Big P Part 1 & 2 -- Contract with EMI, Vinyl Record, 1976 (Box 36, Folder 14)
  - General Correspondence, 1976, 1982 (Box 36, Folder 15)
  - Alain-Philippe Malagnac Correspondence, 1976, 1987 (Box 36, Folder 16)
  - Claudia Ashley -- Contracts, Rights Agreements, Correspondence, 1977 (Box 37, Folder 1-2)
  - X-15 Productions Management Agreement with Thomas Edgar Hurt, 1979-01-26 (Box 37, Folder 3)
  - Notes, General Publicity, 1980s (Box 37, Folder 4)
  - Sugarhill Records -- Original Storyboard Images, 1981-12-14 (Box 37, Folder 5)
  - Trilogy Records, Sasha Rage -- Photographs, Agreements, Lyrics, 1981 (Box 37, Folder 6-7)
  - Richie Havens -- Agreement, Recording Budget Proposal, 1984 (Box 37, Folder 8)
  - Directions for Unknown Recording Session, undated (Box 37, Folder 9)
- Series VI. Personal, 1937-2018; 8 Linear Feet in 8 manuscript boxes, 2 flat boxes, 1 oversize box, and 1 shared cassette box; 1 audiocassette; 603 Megabytes in 1 recording file
  This series consists of material related to Jack Doroshow's personal life, friends, and family. Family photographs from the 1930s to the 1960s contain early images of Jack, his parents, siblings, and extended family. Of note in this series are photographic portraits by Nina Meledandri of Jack and his partner from 1985, as well as candid print and digital images from parties and gatherings at his apartment from the 1980s to the 2010s. Resumes, address books, appointment books, and correspondence provide a view into the daily life of Doroshow and his activities. This series also contains ephemera Doroshow accumulated over the years on friends and partners throughout his life including Bill Wagner, Curtis Carman, Rami Shamir, and granddaughter Zachary Drucker. Doroshow's struggle to retain his rent-stabilized apartment for over 30 years is documented in this series, illustrating the financial struggles of an aging performer in New York City during the 1980s to the 2000s. These files include correspondence with apartment management; photographic documentation of the building management's neglect of the apartment; Doroshow's requests to agencies for rent assistance; and his disbutes with utility companies. This series also contains material related to his legacy as a mentor to the LGBTQ community and drag performers which is evident in his personal correspondence which is full of notes and well-wishes; photographs from 2017 of his last birthday party; documentation of the establishment of the Flawless Sabrina Archives by his friends; and a program from his 2018 memorial service.
  - Photographs -- Jack Doroshow and Family Members, 1937, 1948-1950, undated (Box 37, Folder 10)
  - Appointment and Notes Book, 1964 (Box 38, Folder 1)
  - 1971 Appointment and Notes Book Used in 1980, 1971, 1980 (Box 38, Folder 2)
  - Appointment and Notes Book, circa 1978-1980 (Box 38, Folder 3)
  - Appointment Books, 1979 (Box 38, Folder 4-5)
  - Joe Kanon -- Letter and Photograph with Jack Doroshow, 1973 (Box 50, Folder 2)
  - Partner Harvey Smith's Appointment Book with Additional Jack Doroshow Notes, 1982 (Box 39, Folder 1)
  - Wall Calendar Pages with Appointments and Appearances, 1999-2000 (Box 51, Folder 13)
  - Appointment Book, 2003 (Box 39, Folder 2)
  - Wall Calendar for Jack Doroshow and Harvey Smith, undated (Box 39, Folder 3)
  - Bill Wagner -- Ephemera, Photographs, Letters, 1966-1975 (Box 39, Folder 4-5)
  - Address Books, 1968-2006 (Box 39, Folder 6, Box 40, Folder 1-2)
  - Correspondence, 1968-2017 (Box 40, Folder 3-7, Box 41, Folder 1-3)
  - Photograph -- Jack Doroshow and Rona Jaffee with Her Family, circa 1967-1979 (Box 41, Folder 4)
  - Resumes, 1970s (Box 41, Folder 5)
  - Journal Entry, Writing re: Relationship with Partner JonJon, 1973-06-23 (Box 41, Folder 6)
  - Sections of Spartacus International Gay Guide Book, 1977 (Box 41, Folder 7)
  - Household-Related -- Eviction Notices, Subletting Rooms, Unpaid Bills/Rent, Photographs of Damage, Notes, 1979-1990, 2014, undated (Box 41, Folder 8-9, Box 42, Folder 1-2)
  - Scrapbook -- Notes, Contacts, Household Issues, 1980-1982 (Box 46, Folder 1-2)
  - Drivers Licenses, 1984, 1988 (Box 42, Folder 3)
  - Photographs -- Family Members, Friends, 1984-2008 (Box 42, Folder 4)
  - Drawings and Sketchbooks -- by Jack and Possibly Others, 1984-2009 (Box 42, Folder 5-8)
  - Hand Drawn Cartoons by Jack Doroshow re: His Business and Personal Life, 1985 (Box 51, Folder 14)
  - Photographs by Nina Meledandri -- Portraits of Jack Doroshow and Unknown Partner (Harvey?), 1985 (Box 42, Folder 9, Box 50, Folder 3)
  - Artwork Photograph "The Great Indoors", Including Andy Warhol, Bianca Jagger, circa 1987 (Box 50, Folder 8)
  - Photographs -- Jack Doroshow Portraits, with Friends, at Shows/Events, 1987-2009, undated (Box 42, Folder 10)
  - Curtis Carman -- Original Paintings, Note to Jack, Exhibition Promotional Material, Artist Statement, Performance Piece Footage Whipped, 1998-2012, undated; cuid39114 (Box 42, Folder 11-12, Box Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_594_ER_10)
  - Brief Bio Statement by Jack Doroshow, 2000 (Box 43, Folder 1)
  - Promotional Material for Doroshow Appearances and Events, 2000-2001 (Box 43, Folder 2)
  - Brandon Olsen -- Letters, Sketches, Exhibit Announcements, Notes, 2002-2006 (Box 43, Folder 3)
  - Gary Indiana -- Letters, Artwork, 2003-2007, undated (Box 43, Folder 4)
  - Rami Shamir -- Notes, Letters, Book Train to Pokipse and Related, 2007-2012 (Box 43, Folder 5-6)
  - Jack Doroshow Travel and Research Grant through CUNY BA/BS -- Grant Description, 2010 (Box 43, Folder 7)
  - Nick Solorio -- Letters, Photograph, "Flawless Wig" Series Prints, 2010-2013 (Box 43, Folder 8)
  - Zachary Drucker -- Notes, Letters, Exhibition / Event Ephemera, 2012-2017 (Box 43, Folder 9)
  - Brothers, Sisters, Sons & Daughters Photograph Portfolio by Bruce Weber for Barneys, Spring 2014 (Box 43, Folder 10)
  - Artworks -- "Study 1" Print by Mako Otome and "Brooklyn Style" by Unknown, 2015, undated (Box 43, Folder 11, Box 50, Folder 9)
  - Flawless Sabrina Archive -- Charitable Organization Forms and Papers, 2015 (Box 43, Folder 12)
  - Photographs -- Jack Doroshow Birthday Party at Apartment, 2017-09-10 (Box 43, Folder 13)
  - Jack Doroshow / Flawless Sabrina Memorial Service -- Program and Announcement, 2018-03-18 (Box 43, Folder 14)
  - Doroshow Stationary, Letterhead, and Business Cards, undated (Box 44, Folder 1)
  - Photograph Album "My Day in the Salon with Jack" by Rachel Mares, undated (Box 44, Folder 2)
  - Photographs by Francesco Scavullo -- Portrait of Jack Doroshow, undated (Box 44, Folder 3)
  - Photograph -- Jack Doroshow and Curtis Carman Dressed in Halloween Costumes, undated (Box 44, Folder 4)
  - Erik Landgren -- Letter and Artwork, undated (Box 44, Folder 5)